

# JESÚS MUÑOZ

Web Developer &
Customer Support

## **PROFILE**

With six years of experience in customer service and client support, I have developed strong skills in onboarding, training, troubleshooting, and customer engagement.

Additionally, my three years in software development make me a unique candidate, allowing me to better understand customer needs and achieve objectives more efficiently.

#### CONTACT

+34 655 661 558

jesusmunozpost@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/jesus-munnoz-post

jesusmunnoz.github.io

O Calle Doctor Esquerdo 120

### **LANGUAGES**

Spanish Native

English Professional (C1)
French Basic (B1 - B2)

## **EDUCATION**

# BOOTCAMP (2024 - 2024) Codenotch

Fullstack web developer

DEGREE(2012 - 2016)
Universidad Camilo José Cela
Video Game Design

# FORMACIÓN PROFESIONAL (2008 - 2010) Universidad Francisco de Vitoria

X-Ray Technician

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Codenotch (jul-sep 2024)

## · Web developer

Fullstack web developer. Web design usign HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JavaScript, Node.js, MySQL.

# Carrefour (may-nov 2023)

## BackEnd developer

Cash machine software developer. Development using C/C++.

#### Align Technology (oct 2018 - may 2023)

## Clinical Application Specialist / CAD Designer

Development using C/C++.

Develop and communicate the new generation of treatments with doctors.

Onboard new customer.

3D Smile Designer.

Teach, train, and support our customer. Support and translator for various locations in Europe.

## **Tecnatom (nov 2017- oct 2018)**

#### Unity 3D Developer

E- learning app developer for the nuclear industry.

Development using C#.

2D designer using Autodesk 2D May.

3D designer using Autodesk 3D Max

## Hospital Ntra. Sra. de america (oct 2010-oct 2012)

### X-Ray Technician

Collaborated with a dynamic team in the Radiology, Mammography, and Operating Theater departments, contributing to the seamless operation of medical imaging services.